# Davi Silva Alves de Oliveira

davi.comp.oliveira@gmail.com

Phone: (88) 99766-0734 Fortaleza - CE, Brazil

#### **Profile**

Currently working as a fullstack development intern at Elevar Commerce.

I am an undergraduate student in Information Systems at the Federal University of Ceará - Campus Quixadá, and a web developer with experience in React, Angular, Node, and other development technologies.

My experiences are primarily focused on frontend, but I also work on backend projects using Node and Java.

Check out my projects on my GitHub or connect with me on LinkedIn.

# **Professional Experience**

Dec 2022 - Present | Fullstack Development Intern at Elevar Commerce

• Develop and maintain web applications for an Ecommerce platform, both frontend and backend, including integrations and other features inherent to this type of product;

Skills: Angular · Angular<br/>JS · Angular Universal · Vue · Nuxt · Node · Java · Firebase · SCSS (Sass) · SQL · Rest API · Scrum Methodology

Jul 2021 - Nov 2022 | Frontend Development Scholar at GREat - Computer Networks, Software Engineering, and Systems Group of UFC by FUNCAP

 Develop and maintain web applications focused on order and process management for the State Government of Ceará;

Skills: React · HTML · SCSS (Sass) · Ant Design · Rest API · Scrum Methodology

## **Projects and Technologies**

Click on each project's name to access the respective GitHub repository.

- HTML and CSS:
  - Star Wars Dashboard | 2021
    - \* Sample web application showcasing information about the Star Wars franchise.
- React:
  - User Management Site | 2022
    - \* Simple project for a user management interface.
  - Click Project Site | 2022
    - \* Project for voting on movies for display in a school or institution.

## - Country Quiz | 2022

\* Country quiz with dynamic questions generated from an API with information about countries, cities, etc.

### - Tic-Tac-Toe Game | 2022

\* Simple tic-tac-toe game to play with up to 2 players.

# - Vehicle Rental System Site | 2022

\* Web page for the use of a vehicle rental system for a fictional rental agency in Quixadá.

# • Angular:

### - MFE with Module Federation | 2023

\* Testing the concept of Micro Frontends with Angular applications.

## - Trakto TV | 2023

\* Application made using the Trakto API.

# - Dynamic Layout | 2023

\* Application testing the concept of dynamic layout with Angular.

#### • Vue:

# - Poké Search | 2023

\* Application to list and search for pokémons using the Poké API.

#### - Vehicle Rental System Site | 2022

\* Web page for the use of a vehicle rental system for a fictional rental agency in Quixadá.

### • Node:

#### - Click Project API | 2022

\* Backend for the Click Project, a project for voting on movies for display in a school or institution.

## - Vehicle Rental System API | 2022

\* Backend for the vehicle rental system for a fictional rental agency in Quixadá.

#### • Java:

## - User Management API | 2022

\* Backend for the project of a user management interface.

#### • Kotlin:

	al System $\operatorname{App}\mid 2023$ broid app for the use of a vehicle rental system for a fictional rental age	ency in
Skills		
<ul> <li>Angular;</li> <li>Angular Universal;</li> <li>Vue;</li> <li>React;</li> <li>Node;</li> <li>Java;</li> <li>Typescript;</li> <li>SCSS (Sass);</li> <li>Scrum;</li> <li>Git;</li> <li>PostgreSQL;</li> <li>Prisma.</li> </ul>		
Education		
•	lor of Information Systems - UFC campus Quixadá - CE, Brazil Information Systems with competencies in information system and web develo	opment.
2020 - 2022   Bachelor rupted)	of Computer Engineering - UFC $\it campus$ Quixadá - CE, Brazil (	Inter-
• Bachelor's degree in	Computer Engineering with competencies in embedded systems developmenterrupted for a change of course.	t using
2017 - 2019   Compute	r Networks Technician - IFCE campus Tauá - CE, Brazil	
• Technical education cabling, and comput	in Computer Networks with competencies in network administration, struer maintenance.	ctured
Languages:		
<ul><li>English - Advanced</li><li>Spanish - Beginner</li><li>Portuguese (Brazil</li></ul>	ian) - Native	
Portfolio and Contact (clie	ck to access):	
• GitHub • LinkedIn		

Lattes CVOnline CV

This resume was entirely created in Markdown based on the example available at CV Example.